Indiana University President's Office records, 1963-1990 C459
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative records, 1963-1990; undated (Box 1)
  - Regional Campuses (Box 200)
    - East (Richmond) (Box 203)
      - Annual Report (Box 204)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 204)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 204)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 204)
      - Board of Advisors (Box 204)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 204)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 204)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 204)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 204)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 204)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 204)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 204)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 204)
        - 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 204)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 204)
        - 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 204)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 204)
        - 1983-1985 (Box 204)
        - 1986 (Box 204)
        - 1987 (Box 204)
      - Center for Economic Education, 1979-1980 (Box 204)
      - Guide for Future Physical Development, 1972; (2 folders) (Box 204)
      - NCA Evaluation Visit, 1972 (Box 204)
      - Program Reviews, 1979 (Box 204)
      - Search and Screen (Box 204)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 204)
        - 1986 (Box 204)
        - 1987 (Box 204)
    - Fort Wayne (Box 204)
      - General (Box 204)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 204)
        - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 204)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 204)
        - 1974 (Box 204)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 204)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 205)
        - 1976 (Box 205)
        - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 205)
        - 1977 (Box 205)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 205)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 205)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 205)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 205)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 205)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 205)
        - 1983 (Box 205)
        - 1984 (Box 205)
        - 1985 (Box 205)
        - 1986 (Box 205)
        - 1987 (Box 206)
      - Annual Report (Box 206)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 206)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 206)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 206)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 206)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 206)
      - Airport, President Hansen at, 1976 (Box 206)
      - Athletics, 1976 (Box 206)
      - Board of Advisors (Box 206)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 206)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 206)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 206)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 206)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 206)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 206)
        - 1979, (2 folders) (Box 206)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 206)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 206)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 206)
        - 1983 (Box 206)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 206)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 206)
        - 1986 (Box 206)
      - Budget (Box 206)
        - 1976 (Box 206)
        - 1977 (Box 206)
      - Correspondence (Box 206)
        - 1973 (Box 206)
        - 1975 (Box 206)
        - 1976 (Box 206)
      - Development, 1975-1976 (Box 206)
      - Foundation (Box 206)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 206)
        - 1976-1979 (Box 206)
        - 1985 (Box 206)
        - 1986 (Box 206)
      - Library Gift Report, 1972 (Box 207)
      - Mission Realignment, 1976-1977 (Box 207)
      - Perculator Club, 1985 (Box 207)
      - Search and Screen (Box 207)
        - 1980 (Box 207)
        - 1985 (Box 207)
      - Senate – General Faculty Meetings (Box 207)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 207)
        - 1977 (Box 207)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 207)
        - 1979 (Box 207)
        - 1980 (Box 207)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 207)
        - 1981 (Box 207)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 207)
        - 1982 (Box 207)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 207)
        - 1983-1984, (2 folders) (Box 207)
        - 1984 (Box 207)
        - 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 207)
        - 1985 (Box 207)
        - 1986 (Box 207)
        - 1987 (Box 207)
      - Unification/Merger (Box 207)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 207)
        - 1971-1974 (Box 207)
        - 1972-1981 (Box 207)
    - IUPU - Calumet Advisory Board, 1981 (Box 207)
    - IUPUI (Box 207)
      - General (Box 207)
        - 1971, (2 folders) (Box 208)
        - 1972, (2 folders) (Box 208)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 208)
        - 1973 (Box 208)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 208)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 208)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 208)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 208)
        - 1977 (Box 208)
        - 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 208)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 208)
        - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 208)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 209)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 209)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 209)
        - 1983 (Box 209)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 209)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 209)
        - 1985 (Box 209)
        - 1986 (Box 209)
        - 1987 (Box 209)
      - Annual Report (Box 209)
        - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 209)
        - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 209)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 209)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 209)
        - 38th Street Campus, 1970-1971 (Box 209)
        - Affirmative Action Office, 1976-1977 (Box 209)
        - Alumni Association, 1976-1977 (Box 209)
      - Bepko, Gerald (Box 209)
        - 1986 (Box 209)
        - 1987 (Box 209)
      - Board of Advisors (Box 209)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 209)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 209)
        - 1972-1974 (Box 209)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 209)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 209)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 209)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 209)
        - 1978 (Box 210)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 210)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 210)
        - 1980 (Box 210)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 210)
        - 1981 (Box 210)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 210)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 210)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 210)
        - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 210)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 210)
        - 1985 (Box 210)
        - 1986 (Box 210)
        - 1987 (Box 210)
      - Bookstore, 1972 (Box 210)
      - Budget, 1977-1979 (Box 210)
      - Career Counseling and Placement Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 210)
      - Chancellor Hine, 1972-1973 (Box 210)
      - Clinical Research Center, 1980 (Box 210)
      - Conference Center, 1985 (Box 210)
      - Continuing Studies Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 210)
      - Computer System, 1972-1973 (Box 210)
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 210)
      - Council of Deans (Box 210)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 210)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 210)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 210)
        - 1984 (Box 210)
        - 1985 (Box 210)
        - 1986 (Box 210)
      - Dentistry, School of (Box 210)
        - 1985 (Box 210)
        - 1973-1986 (Box 210)
        - 1987 (Box 210)
        - Search and Screen, 1985 (Box 210)
      - Downtown Campus Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 210)
      - Engineering and Technology (School of) (Box 210)
        - Annual Report (Box 210)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 210)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 210)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 210)
      - Faculty Council (Box 210)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 210)
        - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 210)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 210)
        - 1973 (Box 211)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 211)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 211)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 211)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 211)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 211)
        - 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 211)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 211)
        - 1982 (Box 211)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 211)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 211)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 211)
        - 1986 (Box 211)
        - 1986-1987 (Box 211)
        - 1987 (Box 211)
      - General Items, 1981 (Box 211)
      - Gifts, 1975 (Box 211)
      - Graduate Programs - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 211)
      - Graduate School of Social Service, 1970-1971 (Box 211)
      - Hospitals (Box 211)
        - 1985, (2 folders) (Box 211)
        - 1986 (Box 211)
      - Hospitals Annual Report (Box 211)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 211)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 211)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 212)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 212)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 212)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 212)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 212)
        - 1979-1986 (Box 212)
      - International Programs Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 212)
      - Irwin Newsletters, 1986 (Box 212)
      - Irwin, Glenn (Box 212)
        - 1980 (Box 212)
        - 1986 (Box 212)
      - Land Triangle, 1977 (Box 212)
      - Law (Box 212)
        - General (Box 212)
          - 1973-1974 (Box 212)
          - 1975-1977 (Box 212)
          - 1978 (Box 212)
          - 1985 (Box 212)
          - 1986 (Box 212)
          - 1987 (Box 212)
        - Search and Screen (Box 212)
          - 1981-1982 (Box 212)
          - 1986 (Box 212)
          - 1987 (Box 212)
      - Law Library Gift Reports, 1972 (Box 212)
      - Liberal Arts (School of) - Annual Report (Box 212)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 212)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 212)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 212)
      - Library Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 212)
      - Medical Center (Box 212)
        - Financial Control Committee Meeting Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 212)
        - Housing, 1963-1973 (Box 212)
      - Medical Education (Box 212)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 212)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 212)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 212)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 212)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 212)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 212)
      - Medicine (School of) (Box 212)
        - General (Box 212)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 212)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 212)
          - 1973 (Box 212)
          - 1973 (Box 213)
          - 1973-1974 (Box 213)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 213)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 213)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 213)
          - 1977 (Box 213)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 213)
          - 1978 (Box 213)
          - 1978-1979 (Box 213)
          - 1979-1980 (Box 213)
          - 1980 (Box 213)
          - 1980-1981 (Box 213)
          - 1981-1982 (Box 213)
          - 1984 (Box 213)
          - 1985 (Box 213)
          - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 213)
          - 1987 (Box 213)
        - Annual Report (Box 213)
          - 1970-1971 (Box 213)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 213)
          - 1973-1974 (Box 213)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 213)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 213)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 213)
        - Hospitals (Box 213)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 213)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 213)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 213)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 213)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 213)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 213)
        - Housing, 1971-1972 (Box 213)
        - National Accelerator Laboratory Proposal, 1973 (Box 213)
        - Neo-Moratorium, 1984 (Box 213)
        - Regenstrief Institute for Health Care, 1971-1972 (Box 213)
        - University Medical Associates, 1971-1972 (Box 213)
        - Mental Retardation Center, 1971 (Box 213)
      - Multi-Use Complex, 1979-1980 (Box 214)
      - News Bureau (Box 214)
        - 1985-1986 (Box 214)
        - 1987 (Box 214)
      - Nursing, School of (Box 214)
        - General (Box 214)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 214)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 214)
          - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 214)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 214)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 214)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 214)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 214)
          - 1978-1979 (Box 214)
          - 1979-1980 (Box 214)
          - 1981, (2 folders) (Box 214)
          - 1982-1983 (Box 214)
          - 1983 (Box 214)
          - 1984 (Box 214)
          - 1984-1985 (Box 214)
          - 1985 (Box 214)
          - 1986 (Box 214)
          - 1987 (Box 214)
        - Annual Report (Box 214)
          - 1970-1971 (Box 214)
          - 1973-1974 (Box 214)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 214)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 214)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 214)
          - 1985-1986 (Box 214)
      - Senior Nursing Loan, 1975 (Box 214)
      - Personnel Reports (Box 214)
        - 1980 (Box 214)
        - 1981 (Box 214)
        - 1982 (Box 214)
        - 1983 (Box 214)
        - 1984 (Box 214)
        - 1986 (Box 214)
        - 1987 (Box 214)
      - Physical Education (Box 214)
        - General (Box 214)
          - 1977 (Box 214)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 214)
        - Annual Report (Box 214)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 214)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 214)
      - Physical Plant (Box 214)
        - Annual Report (Box 214)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 214)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 214)
          - 1978-1979 (Box 214)
      - Police Department Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 215)
      - Program Reviews, 1981-1983 (Box 215)
      - Registrar's Office Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 215)
      - Research Grant Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 215)
      - Research and Sponsored Programs (Box 215)
        - General, 1979 (Box 215)
        - Annual Report (Box 215)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 215)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 215)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 215)
          - 1979-1980 (Box 215)
          - 1980-1981 (Box 215)
      - Riley Hospital - Proposed Parking Structure, 1974 (Box 215)
      - Safety, Division of, 1973 (Box 215)
      - Scholarships and Financial Aid (Box 215)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 215)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 215)
      - Science, School of (Box 215)
        - General, 1976 (Box 215)
        - Annual Report (Box 215)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 215)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 215)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 215)
          - 1978-1979 (Box 215)
          - 1980-1981 (Box 215)
      - Search and Screen (Box 215)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 215)
        - 1985 (Box 215)
        - 1986 (Box 215)
      - Student Services - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 215)
      - Summary Statement - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 215)
      - Surgery, Department of (Box 215)
        - Annual Report (Box 215)
          - 1972-1973 (Box 215)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 215)
          - 1976-1977 (Box 215)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 215)
          - 1979-1980 (Box 215)
      - University Reorganization, 1974 (Box 215)
      - 1982 (Box 215)
    - Kokomo (Box 215)
      - General (Box 215)
        - 1967-1970 (Box 215)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 215)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 215)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 215)
        - 1974 (Box 215)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 215)
        - 1975 (Box 215)
        - 1974-1976 (Box 215)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 215)
        - 1976 (Box 215)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 215)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 216)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 216)
        - 1979, (2 folders) (Box 216)
        - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 216)
        - 1980 (Box 216)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 216)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 216)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 216)
        - 1983 (Box 216)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 216)
        - 1984 (Box 216)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 216)
        - 1985 (Box 216)
        - 1986 (Box 216)
        - 1987 (Box 216)
      - Annual Report (Box 216)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 216)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 216)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 216)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 216)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 216)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 216)
      - Board of Advisors (Box 216)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 216)
        - 1972-1976 (Box 216)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 216)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 216)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 216)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 216)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 216)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 216)
        - 1980 (Box 216)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 216)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 216)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 217)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 217)
        - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 217)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 217)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 217)
        - 1986 (Box 217)
      - Bookstore, 1971-1972 (Box 217)
      - Gifts, 1972 (Box 217)
      - Reaction to IHEC Recommendation to Reduce IUK to Junior College Level, 1972 (Box 217)
      - Ryan's Visit, 1983 (Box 217)
    - Northwest (Box 217)
      - General (Box 217)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 217)
        - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 217)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 217)
        - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 217)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 217)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 217)
        - 1977 (Box 217)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 217)
        - 1978 (Box 217)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 217)
        - 1979 (Box 217)
        - 1980 (Box 217)
        - 1981 (Box 217)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 217)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 217)
        - 1983 (Box 217)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 217)
        - 1984 (Box 217)
        - 1985 (Box 217)
        - 1986 (Box 217)
        - 1987 (Box 217)
      - Annual Report (Box 217)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 217)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 218)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 218)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 218)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 218)
      - Board of Advisors (Box 218)
        - 1972 (Box 218)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 218)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 218)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 218)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 218)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 218)
        - 1977 (Box 218)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 218)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 218)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 218)
        - 1980 (Box 218)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 218)
        - 1981 (Box 218)
        - 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 218)
        - 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 218)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 218)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 218)
        - 1986 (Box 218)
      - Dean of Faculties Teaching Improvement Project, 1976 (Box 218)
      - Dental Letters, 1972 (Box 218)
      - Dentistry Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 218)
      - Hernandez, Leodoro, 1980 (Box 218)
    - South Bend (Box 218)
      - General (Box 218)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 218)
        - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 218)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 218)
        - 1974 (Box 219)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 219)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 219)
        - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 219)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 219)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 219)
        - 1979 (Box 219)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 219)
        - 1980, (2 folders) (Box 219)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 219)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 219)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 219)
        - 1983 (Box 219)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 219)
        - 1984 (Box 219)
        - 1985 (Box 219)
        - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 219)
        - 1987 (Box 219)
      - Annual Report (Box 219)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 219)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 219)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 219)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 219)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 219)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 219)
      - Associates Building (Box 219)
        - 1974-1979 (Box 219)
        - 1980 (Box 219)
        - 1981 (Box 219)
        - 1983 (Box 219)
      - Board of Advisors (Box 219)
        - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 220)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 220)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 220)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 220)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 220)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 220)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 220)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 220)
        - 1980, (2 folders) (Box 220)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 220)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 220)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 220)
        - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 220)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 220)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 220)
        - 1986 (Box 220)
      - Faculty, 1980 (Box 220)
      - Gifts (Box 220)
        - 1972 (Box 220)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 220)
      - A Guide for Physical Development, 1967 (Box 220)
      - Mental Retardation Program, 1971-1972 (Box 220)
      - News Items (Box 220)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 220)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 220)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 220)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 220)
      - Newsletters, 1980 (Box 220)
      - Operations Review, 1976 (Box 220)
      - Program Reviews, 1981-1983 (Box 220)
      - Ryan's Visit to Elkhart, 1971 (Box 220)
      - Savage Report, 1974-1975 (Box 220)
      - Special Services Project, 1980 (Box 220)
      - Senate Minutes (Box 220)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 220)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 220)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 220)
    - Southeast (Box 220)
      - General (Box 220)
        - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 220)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 220)
        - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 221)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 221)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 221)
        - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 221)
        - 1977 (Box 221)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 221)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 221)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 221)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 221)
        - 1981-1982 (Box 221)
        - 1983 (Box 221)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 221)
        - 1984 (Box 221)
        - 1985 (Box 221)
        - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 221)
        - 1987 (Box 221)
      - Annual Report (Box 221)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 221)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 221)
        - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 221)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 221)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 222)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 222)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 222)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 222)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 222)
      - Board of Advisors (Box 222)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 222)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 222)
        - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 222)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 222)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 222)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 222)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 222)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 222)
        - 1980 (Box 222)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 222)
        - 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 222)
        - 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 222)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 222)
        - 1984 (Box 222)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 222)
        - 1986 (Box 222)
      - Bookstore, 1971-1972 (Box 222)
      - Gifts - Scholarship and Financial Aid, 1976-1977 (Box 222)
      - A Guide for Future Physical Development, 1976-1977 (Box 222)
      - Mission Statement Development, 1971-1972 (Box 222)
      - Program Reviews, 1979-1983 (Box 222)
      - Search and Screen, 1985 (Box 222)
    - Whitewater College Programs, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 222)
  - Register (Box 222)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 222)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 222)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 222)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 222)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 222)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 222)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 222)
  - Registrar (Box 222)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 222)
    - 1986 (Box 222)
    - 1987 (Box 222)
  - Registrar's Office (Box 222)
    - General (Box 222)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 222)
      - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 222)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 222)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 222)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 222)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 222)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 222)
    - Annual Report (Box 222)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 222)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 222)
      - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 222)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 222)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 222)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 222)
      - 1980-1981, (2 folders) (Box 222)
  - Registration (Box 222)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 222)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 222)
  - Registration Center, 1985 (Box 222)
  - Religion and Intellectual Life (Box 222)
    - 1986 (Box 223)
    - 1987 (Box 223)
  - Religions, 1978 (Box 223)
  - Religious Studies, 1972-1985 (Box 223)
  - Report of Self-Evaluation, 1972 (Box 223)
  - Reorganization (Box 223)
    - General, 1973 (Box 223)
    - Task Force on University Organization (Box 223)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 223)
      - 1971-1975 (Box 223)
  - Representation Fund (Indiana University Foundation) (Box 223)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 223)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 223)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 223)
  - Republican Governors' Association Conference, 1971 (Box 223)
  - Requests (Box 223)
    - 1973 (Box 223)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 223)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 223)
  - Requisitions - Archives, 1983 (Box 223)
  - Research (Box 223)
    - General (Box 223)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 223)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 223)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 223)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 223)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 223)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 223)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 223)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 223)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 223)
      - 1983 (Box 223)
    - Kidney Stone Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 223)
  - Research and Advanced Studies (Box 223)
    - General (Box 223)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 223)
      - 1972 (Box 223)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 223)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 223)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 223)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 223)
    - Annual Report (Box 223)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 223)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 223)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 223)
      - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 224)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 224)
    - GRAS Pending, 1969-1971 (Box 224)
  - Research Centers, 1980 (Box 224)
  - Research Center for Applied Science (Box 224)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 224)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 224)
  - Research Center for the Language and Semiotic Studies (Box 224)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 224)
    - 1972 (Box 224)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 224)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 224)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 224)
    - 1977 (Box 224)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 224)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 224)